同志们 我不骗你们哦
Guys, I'm not gonna lie.
上个月本人经历了好多
It has been one hell of a month for old Pen.
悔婚 死宅
Broken engage, infested condo,
Glen Beck把他的手指都塞到我嘴里
Glen Beck put his fingers in my mouth.
上次我们去他图书签售会就这样 好讽刺
That's the last time we go to one of his book signings ironically.
是啊 好讽刺
Yeah. Ironically.
不过我确实要感谢暂住舍友Brad和Jane
But I do wanna thank my temporary roomies Brad and Jane
热情好客 还有一大堆羊毛绒绒
for your hospitality, your support, and your vast collection of cashmere throws.
最讨厌棉料了
Cotton irritates my nipsey russells.
提到咱们人生中的布料时 注意点啊
Hey, watch your mouth when you're talking about the fabric of our lives.
我愿意说棉花就说棉花 关你事
I think I've earned the right to talk about cotton any way I damn well please.
你说得对 先生
I believe you have, sir.
我内心很是窃喜 你的真命天子久不出现
I'm secretly glad that your exterminator's taking so long.
跟我们在一起多好 就像小家庭
It's been so nice having you stay with us. We're like a-a little family.
是啊 Brad是爸爸 Jane是妈妈
Yeah, Brad's the dad, Jane's the mom,
Penny是发育良好的小孩
and Penny's the little baby with the thick knockers.
肯定是遗传我们家族的基因
Which she clearly got from my side of the family.
不是吗 基因优秀 丰乳肥臀
What? She got them big thangs. You got them bee stings.
- 是啊 - 挺好
- Yeah, I do. - All right.
- 行了 - 好恶
- Okay, okay... - Gross.
- 你好啊 Penny - 你好 Shaun
- Hey, Penny! - Hey, Shaun!
关于给你的健身音乐合辑 我想跟你道歉
Hey, I wanna apologize for that workout mix I gave you.
还有好多都比Ezra强
There was way too much better than Ezra on there.
挺好的 我都不知道他们不止有一首歌
No, it was great. I didn't even know they had more than one song.
行吧 我们瘦身造型馆见咯
All right, cool. I'll see you in cardio sculpt?
瘦身造型馆?
Cardio sculpt?
- 我也希望呢 再见 - 再见
- I hope to. Bye. - Bye.
那正太是谁啊
Oh. Who was that slice of peach pie?
- 好萌 对吧 - 萌到深处 Penny
- Cute, right? - Suh kyut, Penny.
你该领他去骨头镇
I mean, you should take him to Bone Town.
你知道Halsted的肋关节吧 我爱那地方
You know that rib joint on Halsted? I love that place.
我也不知道 他约过我 但是...
I don't know. He asked me out, but...
我觉得自己还没准备好重新恋爱
I don't think I'm ready for another relationship yet.
跟Pete的分手 就像坐过山车
I mean, this whole Pete thing has been such a roller coaster.
上上下下 呕吐不止
Ups, downs, barfing.
我还...好难过呢
I just... I'm still pretty bummed out.
我懂你 宝贝
I know you are, sweetie,
不过没人说要恋爱 好吗
but no one's talking about a relationship, okay?
你就暧昧一下 不用当真
You need a fling, nothing serious.
我想到了
I have got it.
我要在家给你和Shaun 办一次无压力的四人约会
I am gonna host a no pressure, double dinner date for you and Shaun at our place.
基友闺蜜 都别拒绝
And like five out of five frat guys, I am not gonna take no for an answer.
来吧!
Do it! Do it! Do it! Do it!
好了 我给他打电话
All right! Okay! Okay! I'll call him.
谢谢
Thank you.
各位 收起钱包
Guys, put your wallets away
因为这顿晚餐 我来请
because this dinner is on me.
跑啊
Run!
各位 这招瞒天过海的"晚餐我请快跑"
Guys, what part of "dinner's on me, flawless diversion, run!"
你们不懂啊
did you not understand?
哥们 不能在Rosalita这里吃完就跑
Dude, you can't dine and dash at Rosalita's.
我们一天能来六次
We come here, like, six times a day.
我知道 我现在是穷得身无分文
I know. I am just, like, hella broke right now.
看好了 刚拿来本月月租
Hey! Just droppin' off this month's rent.
大哥 你找份工作吧
Dude, you gotta get a job.
我知道 我是要找工作
I know. I-I'm gonna get a job.
但我得先借一千美元 做简历 付房租
I just need to borrow, like, a thousand dollars for my resume.  And rent.
买一条办公用的正式领带 还有啤酒
And a business formal tie. And beer.
还有去参加面试的车 还有青蛙服装
And transportation to a job interview. And a frog costume.
- 青蛙服装? - 不用说了 哥们
- Frog costume? - Oh, say no more, my friend.
这钱我给你
I got extra money for that.
<font color=#38B0DE>-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Proudly Presents</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: Bella Iphigenie cici 校对: 王棫垚 时间轴: 有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Sync:óD???à?ê</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>幸福终点站 第三季 第20集</font>
<font color=#70DB93>Happy.Endings S3 Ep20</font>
Jane 咚咚 Brad快递上门
Knock, knock, Jane! Brad delivery service.
我们收了个翘臀 给你来送了哟
We pick that sweet ass up and bring that sweet ass home.
Sarofsky先生
Uh, Mr. Sarofsky.
Jane说这里有个月光酒吧
Jane said there was a luna bar in here.
我要雌激素 弄掉背上的发茬
I need the estrogen. I'm trying to get rid of the stubble on my back.
恶 我是说...酷
Uch! I mean, cool.
那么 夫人呢
So how's-- how's the missus?
- 你说Candice呀 - 是啊
- Oh.  Candice? - Yeah.
她完美地...诠释了什么是贱人
She's great... at being a huge bitch.
她把我从家里赶出来了 Brad
She kicked me out of the house, Brad,
她给我来一句莫向老娘怨别离
and now she's slapping me in the face with a big "D."
- 什么 - 离婚
- I'm sorry? - Divorce.
哎 我好抱歉 朋友
listen, I'm sorry to hear that, man.
如果你想谈心的话
Look, if you ever wanna talk--
我想啊 太好了 就今晚吧
Yeah, I do. That'd be great. How about tonight?
有晚宴
dinner party.
Jane和我今晚有晚宴 所以...
Jane and I have a dinner party tonight, so...
好吧
All right.
反正我也无家可归
Well, I'll just hang out here anyway,
没准得睡在车上
probably sleep in a Corolla.
独自一人 辗转反侧
All alone, by myself,
像无助的孩子 痛苦呻吟
crying like a baby trapped in a well.
你想来参加我们的晚宴吗
Do you wanna join us for dinner?
汽车沙皇会在女厕装摄像头吗
Does the Car Czar have a camera in the women's bathroom?
不会 我不会 也不想
No, I do not and would not,
不过 是的 我想去参加晚宴
but, yeah, I wanna come over for dinner.
- 好极了 - 我准备好可以走了
- Right on. - Hey, Boo. I'm ready to go.
好 有件小事
Great. Uh, a tiny adorable addendum.
汽车沙皇也来吃晚餐
Car Czar's coming over for dinner.
多好啊 是不是
Isn't that great?
白痴 现在满意了吗
'Sup, shmorons. Happy now?
说什么呢 然后你怎么进来的
What do you mean? And how did you get in here?
你为什么穿我的睡衣
And why are you wearing my robe?
我有钥匙 睡衣我拒绝解释
I have keys, and I refuse to explain the robe.
你们记得催我快点找工作吧
You guys remember how you were on me to get a job?
我找到了一个更好的赚钱方法
Well, I found an even better way to make some money.
我去参加芝加哥超钙先生比赛
I'm gonna be a contestant in Mr. Super Gay Chicago.
满意了吗
Happy now?
满意了吗 是这么说的
Oh, that's where that "happy now?" Goes.
- 什么先生 - 超钙什么
- Mr. what? - Super gay where?
每年Rosalita举办都芝加哥超钙先生比赛
The super gay pageant they have every year at Rosalita's.
头等奖一千块
Grand prize is 1,000 bucks.
还有啥赚钱方法好过
What better way to make some cash
高危莫测的主观竞赛?
than a high-risk, unpredictable, subjective contest?
简单易上手啊
I mean, it's foolproof.
Max 我们说的"找工作"不是这意思
Max, when we said "get a job," this is not what we meant.
- 这个好太多了 - 逆天了
- This is so much better! - It's awesome!
我绝对能帮到你
And I can totally help you.
"Toddlers和Tiaras" 我每集都看了
I have seen every episode of "Toddlers & Tiaras,"
"比赛王" "小皇后" 和 "皇后王"
"Pageant Kings," "Baby Queens," and "King Of Queens."
- 最后一个是所有人都赢的闹剧 - 当然啊
- That last one is just a pageant of comedy where everyone wins.- Of course.
我也能帮忙 我小时候
And I can help, too. When I was a kid,
得过少年先生的地区赛冠军 青年的比赛
I was regional champ at junior mister, the young gentlemen's pageant.
你小时候就参加过竞赛
You were in pageants as a kid?
纠正下你 长官 我小时候赢过竞赛
Uh, correction, officer. I won pageants as a young adult.
谢谢 你们俩
Thanks, guys.
咱俩任重道远啊
We have a lot of work to do.
你怎么能邀请汽车沙皇过来呢
How could you invite the Car Czar over?
他明显喝醉了 搞砸了Shaun和Penny的约会
He's clearly drunk and ruining Shaun and Penny's date.
对不起 我当时很囧 一慌神就叫他了
I'm sorry. When I'm in an awkward situation, I panic and invite people to things...
就像我邀请商场圣诞老人来咱俩的婚礼
like when I invited that mall Santa to our wedding.
对哦 我忘不了Darryl的 别担心
Oh, yeah. I can't forget Darryl. Don't worry.
谁饿啦
Who's hungry?
Janie...肉在哪呀
Whoa! Janie...  Where's the meat course? Huh?
到目前为止 这顿饭好像是Moby招待的
So far it feels like this dinner's been catered by Moby.
这是给Shaun的素食餐
It is a vegetarian meal for Shaun,
我们想邀请并邀请来的客人
the guest we wanted and therefore invited.
Shaun 你说完全蛋白质是怎么回事来着
Now, Shaun, what were you saying about complete proteins again?
大米青豆什锦饭能提供给你 所需要的全部氨基酸
You can get all the amino acids you need from a rice-bean combo.
哟 Shaun
Oh, Shaun!
Shaun 拜托
Shaun! Come on!
吃肉才能长肉肉
Meat is what makes your meat work.
- 苍天啊 - 好了
- Oh, God. - Okay.
Shaun 我懂四人约会 好吗
Shaun, listen. I get the whole double date thing, okay?
我不想让你在朋友们前面出丑
And I don't wanna embarrass you in front of your gal.
但我真心觉得 咱们应该摔跤
But... I really think we should wrestle.
- 什么 - 什么
- What? - What?
对头 我赢了 大家吃牛排
Yeah. I win, we eat steak.
你赢了 往后闭嘴 好吗
You win, you shut up for the rest of your life. Huh?
觉得怎样 小玉米 来吧 开始
What do you say, baby corn? Let's go. Let's go. Let's get this off.
- 你也想舒活舒活筋骨是吧 - 别...
- You're gonna wanna move comfortably. - Don't--
- 脱衣服 来吧 - 天 好吧
- Let's get undressed. Let's get this off. - Whoa. Okay.
- 来脱光 - 好吧 这样有点奇葩
- Let's get naked. - Uh, o-okay. This-- this is getting weird.
咱就要奇葩
Yeah, let's get weird.
- 我要走了 抱歉 Penny - 别 Shaun
- Um, I'm gonna go. Sorry, Penny. Sorry, Penny.- No, Shaun.
我们来奇葩吗
Let's get weird.
- 不 我要走了 - 别整什么奇葩 Shaun
- No, I gotta go. I gotta go. -Shaun-- let's not get weird. Shaun!
你不是要跟我们讲小扁豆的吗
You were gonna tell us about lentils!
- 他大姨夫来了吧 - 你什么毛病啊
- Must be his time of the month, huh? - What the hell is wrong with you?
我回房间了
I'm going to my room.
- Freddie叔叔 - 你们起来啦
- Uncle Freddie! - Oh, you're up.
又来啊 你怎么进来的
Again? How did you get in here?
我睡这了
I slept here.
芝加哥超钙先生比赛 咱得开始训练了
Okay, we need to work on my training for Mr. Super Gay Chicago.
我昨晚去了情况说明会 竞争可激烈了
I went to orientation last night, and the competition is stiff.
<font color=#FFFF33>stiff也有硬了的意思</font>
硬了那人被取消了资格
They disqualified that guy,
但剩下的竞争还是挺强的
but the rest of the competition is pretty good.
好嘞 我们开始吧
Okay, let's get started.
我来教你我94年少年先生获胜的编排
I'm gonna teach you my winning routine from Junior Mister '94.
那可是无与伦比
It was the cream de la cream.
Dave 11岁
Dave, age 11
Dave 这都31世纪了 好咩
Uh, Dave, welcome to the 31st century. Okay?
Max 要想赢 你需要闪闪闪 火火火
Max, to win, you need flash, flash, flash, and fire.
不 相信我
No. Trust me,
作为自愿的直男前选美选手 小型兄弟会的一员
as a member of the small fraternity of willing, straight male pageant veterans,
我知道你需要更稀有的东西
I know you need something a little more rare.
- 格调 - 随便啦
- Class. - Whatever.
有好多项目 我们就平分吧
There's a bunch of categories, so we'll just divide it up.
Dave 你负责问答和才艺 Alex 你负责夜店装和钙男健身
Dave, you'll take Q&A and Talent. Alex, you'll take Clubwear and Gay Fitness.
好吧 只要Alex不搞砸
Fine, as long as Alex doesn't mess this up.
你是把我跟你的发型师搞混了吧
Uh, I think you have me confused with your hairstylist.
放心啦
Count it.
我还会负责冷酷无情的反驳
I'll also be covering the category of stone-cold bitchy comebacks.
噢耶!
Yeah, babe!
发生什么事
What just happened?
Pen 我只是想为 你昨晚的约会被毁而道歉
Hey, Pen. I just wanted to apologize for your date getting ruined last night.
我很抱歉...Brad邀请了汽车沙皇
I feel terrible... that Brad invited the Car Czar.
谢谢你来道歉
Well, thank you for the apology. I appreciate it.
但我要去准备上班了 所以晚点见吧
But I gotta get ready for work so I'll see you guys later, okay? Bye!
宝贝 我打开焦糖了 快扭着小屁股过来
Babe, I got the caramel open. Get your buns in here.
我...的...天
Oh... my.. goodness.
Penny犯了个小错误
Penny made a boo-boo.
Jane 你得帮我脱身
Jane, you gotta get me out of this!
关上门 你们是住在谷仓里吗
Hey! Close the door! What, do you live in a barn?!
所以这就是为什么 你跟Penny约会是个烂主意
So that's why you and Penny seeing each other is a... bad idea.
是啊 我是说...
Yeah. Yeah, I mean...
谢谢你提醒我 Jane
Thank you for the heads-up, Jane.
我完全不知道她是民主党人
I had... no idea she was a Democrat.
我会避开那个亲工会的贱人的
Well, I am gonna steer clear of that pro-Union whore.
谢啦
Thank you.
- 你成功脱身了 - 感谢上帝
- So you're out of it. - Oh, thank God!
谢谢你 Jane 你救了我一命
Thank you, Jane. You have saved my life.
宝贝 从一到令人垂涎 你给我的电臀打几分
Babe, what do you think of my tushie on a scale from 1 to mouthwatering?
你怎么回事
What is wrong with you?
首先 他是我上司
First of all, he is my boss.
其次 他是我见过最恶心的人
Second of all, he is the grossest man I have ever met.
他在车店后面那家脱衣舞俱乐部 有长期订单 店名叫蛋蛋
He has a standing order at the strip club behind the dealership-- eggs.
我知道 但我从来没跟 他这样的人在一起过
I know, but I've never been with a guy like him before.
他傲慢又老派
He's brash and old-school,
就像喝两倍的酒 却只有一半头发的Don Draper
like Don Draper with twice the drinking and half the hair.
加上性爱超级美妙
Plus the sex is amazing.
好了 麻烦别批评我 拜
Okay, please don't judge me! Bye!
我们没谈完呢
We are not done talking about this!
我错了 我错了 大错特错
Mistake. Mistake. Mistake. Mistake.
好了 超钙先生的问答环节十分重要
Okay, Max, the Mr. Super Gay Chicago Q&A section is crucial.
第一个问题 菜肉蛋饼还是乳蛋饼
First question-- frittata or quiche?
- 这个嘛 - 回答错误
- Well--  - Wrong answer.
我都还没回答呢
I didn't even answer.
别咬文嚼字 Max
Don't be so literal, Max.
Dave Matthews唱"蚂蚁行军" 是因为他想看蚂蚁行军咩
Does Dave Matthews sing "Ants Marching" because he wants to see ants marching?
我不知道 他是天才 这不关我们事
I don't know. The man's a genius. It's none of our business.
重点是 这是风格问题
The point is, it's about style.
看到这没
Now you see this?
这叫做沉思手
These are called ponder hands.
让我看起来像在深思问题
They make me look like I'm pondering the answer.
现在换你 你沉思时 手会放哪
Now you try. Where do you put your hands when you ponder?
不对 该死
No, damn it!
这什么
What's this?
这是Alex让你穿的夜店装吗
Is this what Alex has you wearing in Clubwear?
天啊 实在太...
Oh, my God. That is absolutely...
糟糕? 他这样说我的夜店装?
Terrible? That's what he said about my Clubwear?
不好意思 但你好看极了
I'm sorry, Max, but you look amazing.
你确定吗 Alex
Are you sure, Alex?
因为漏风呢 哪儿都漏
'Cause there's a breeze, like... everywhere.
让人记住总比无聊好
It's better to be memorable than boring.
你想当Russell Brand 还是Russell乏味
Do you want to be Russell Brand or Russell bland?
只有这俩选择吗
Are those my only two options?
你必须表现得比整场比赛都大气
You have to act like you're bigger than this whole competition.
忘记沉思手吧
Forget ponder hands.
你要练练翻白眼
You need to practice your eye rolls.
来吧 给爹地翻一个
Come on. Throw some shade for papa.
不够大气
Not big enough.
我要看到只有眼白
I wanna see only whites.
深色瞳孔翻到后面去
Dark pupils right to the back.
<font color=#FFFF33>歧义:黑人学生坐到后面去</font>
我也发现这话说得有问题了
I realize that that sounds bad.
你想看起来恼怒时 会怎么做
Okay, what do you do when you wanna look annoyed?
该死 不行 Max
Damn it! No, Max.
- 你怎么了 Penny - 你真是一团糟
- What is going on with you, Penny? - You are a mess.
你看着就像拆掉辫子的Coolio
You look like Coolio after he takes his braids out.
<font color=#FFFF33>自行谷歌图片吧</font>
我无法停止跟那位波兰穴居人上床
I can't stop having sex with that Polish caveman.
我甚至不喜欢他 他让我恶心
I don't even like him. I mean, he disgusts me.
但他有种神奇的掌控力 有时候是真的掌控
But he has this magical hold on me. And sometimes a real hold.
你们试过被上四方压制么
You ever gotten caught up in a North-South keylock?
<font color=#FFFF33>搏击术语 基本类似69= =</font>
- 站着还是坐着 - 都有
- Standing up or sitting down? - Both.
- 好了 Brad别跑题 - 好
- Okay, Brad, stay on message. - Right.
Penny 我带着满满的爱对你说...
Penny, I say this with all the love in my heart--
你真让我厌恶
you're disgusting to me.
Jane 我知道好么
Jane, I know. Okay,
但我觉得我已经摆脱了
but look, I think I've gotten it out of my system.
好哇 好吧
Okay. Okay.
天啊 我没邀他来 我发誓
Oh, my God. I did not invite him here, I swear!
该死
Crap.
他对我也有种神奇的掌控力嘛
He has a magical hold over me, too.
我哪都不想他出现 但我却总邀请他
I don't want him anywhere, but I have to invite him everywhere.
汽那个车那个沙皇 就要吃起早午餐 像个摇滚明星
Hey! C-A-R to the Czar, 'bout to brunch it up like... a rock star!
- 好吧 你在乐队里 - 我不想那样做的
- Okay, you're in a band. - I didn't want to do that.
Jane 你今天得帮我做季度报告
I need you to do those quarterly reports for me today.
我昨晚没弄因为我在 引号 反引号
I didn't get to 'em last night 'cause I was quote, unquote,
忙着跟我左边这人做爱呢
busy making sex with the person to my left.
麻烦继续别批评我
Please continue not to judge me.
我觉得这奶油变质了
I think that whipped cream has turned.
大家好呀
Hello, everyone!
欢迎来到芝加哥第二钙的 选美比赛的第一晚
Welcome to the first night of Chicagoland's second gayest pageant.
我是主持人Josh Jill
I'm your host Josh Jill.
- 这太酷啦 - 就是啊
- This is so cool! - I know.
我上一次这么激动
I haven't been this excited since I found out
还是发现Donnie Wahlberg跟我 同一天生日的时候
Donnie Wahlberg and I share the same birthday.
好啦 差一天
Well, one day apart.
第一个项目是钙男健身
Our first category is Gay Fitness,
就像普通健身 只是更基
which is just like fitness, only gayer.
真是超基精彩
That was gay-rific.
说到胖 有请Max Blum
Speaking of fat, here's Max Blum.
好耶
Yes!
慢着 这什么玩意 我不是这样跟他说的
Wait. What the hell is that? That's not what I told him.
确实不是
No, it's not.
现在他是一位有格调有尊严的健美绅士
Now he's a classy, dignified, gentleman of fitness.
这本该是我负责的项目
This was supposed to be my category.
Max 顶
Psst, Max! Max, thrust!
顶一个
Thrust! Add a thrust!
别听她的 Max
Don't listen to her, Max.
踏步 伸展 踏步 伸展
March and expand! March and expand!
- 微笑 微笑 - 顶 顶
- And smile! Smile! - Thrust! Thrust!
- 抬起膝盖 抬膝盖 - 别
- Get those knees up! Knees up. - No!
膝盖抬高 这就对了
Knees up. There it is. There it is.
好吧 那真是我见过最糟的事
Okay, that's literally the worst thing I've ever seen,
<font color=#FFFF33>美国第一位女性国务卿 76岁</font>
我还在Instagram上关注了 Madeleine Albright呢
and I follow Madeleine Albright on Instagram.
好嘞好嘞
All right, all right.
那么...
So...
手工艺博物馆有个中世纪勺子展览
There's an exhibit on mid-century spoons at the craft museum.
哇哦 我喜欢
Wow. I love...
好勺子
a good spoon.
- 可能很有意思哦 - 是的
- Yeah. Could be interesting. - Yeah.
- 应该不错 - 嗯
- Could be good. - Mm.
上车啦
All aboard!
这是我的票 先生
Here's my ticket, sir!
那不是这趟火车的票
That's not the ticket for this train.
不 会怎么样呢
Oh, no! What's gonna happen?!
这里说...
Oh, says here...
他们有猫王用来量牛轧糖的勺子呢
They have a spoon that Elvis used to measure out a nougat. Huh?
我不干了
I'm out!
他们让我崩了 估计床也崩了
They broke me. And probably the guess bed.
天哪 这选美简直就是同志灾难
Ahh. God. This pageant is a gay disaster.
比我看见Bette Midler骑在马上那次还糟
It's worse than the time I saw Bette Midler get on a horse.
问答环节太吃力了
I mean, that Q&A was rough.
我不知道你怎么回事 怪胎
Okay, I don't know what's going on with you, creepy,
不过我得要你回答
but I need an answer.
慕斯还是冻糕
The question is, mousse or parfait?
- 沉思手势不错 Max - 翻白眼 再翻过去些
- Good ponder hands, Max! - Roll your eyes! More!
我翻过头了 我要倒了
I've-- I've over-- I've overrolled.  Overrolled. Going down.
同志倒下了 超级同志倒了
Gay down! Super gay down!
Max 我们现在得增加格调
Max, what we need to do now is double down on the class.
没门
No way!
Max 你得闪眼
Max, you need flash.
闪粉 绸缎 臀缝 一起上
Okay, I am talking glitter, satin, butt crack.
什么 你疯了么
What?! Are you crazy?
同志选美没臀缝的事
Butt crack has no place in a gay beauty pageant.
- 什么 - 你俩都给我闭嘴
- What?! - Okay, both of you shut it.
我同意参加
The only reason I did this thing
只是因为不喜欢总是最穷那个
is because I'm sick of being the poor one all the time.
太难堪了
It's embarrassing.
我请你们帮忙
And I asked you two for help,
你们却反过来以自己为中心
and you turned it around and made it all about you.
不好意思 你们俩都被开除了
Now if you'll excuse me, you're both fired.
回头见 美胸甜心
Later, honey boobs-boobs.
是你们啊
Hey, it's you!
我本想夸奖你们的
You know, I've been meaning to compliment you.
你们突然出现的本事太神奇了
Your coming out of nowhere has just gotten amazing.
可我累了
Well, tired.
慢着 小姐 我们得谈谈汽车沙皇的问题
Not so fast, young lady. We need to talk about the Car Czar.
我和Brad觉得他对你是个不良影响 是时候冷一冷了
Brad and I feel he's a bad influence on you and maybe it's time to slow it down.
我们不是生气 只是很失望
We're not mad! We're just disappointed!
好吧 怎么了
Okay.  What's going on?
我和Brad商量过了
Brad and I have discussed it,
我们不许你再见汽车沙皇
and we forbid you from seeing the Car Czar ever again.
你们禁止我?
Uh, you forbid me?
喂 你们又不是我老板
Hellur. You're not the boss of me.
Pradesh Singh 环球公关公司一把手 才是我的老板
Pradesh Singh, the head of Global PR, is the boss of me.
虽然她休产假去了
Although she may be going on maternity leave,
现在老板也许是Nancy Goldberg
so it's probably gonna be Nancy Goldberg.
少来 嬉皮士才休产假
Please. Maternity leave is for hippies.
你要想在我们家住 就得听我们的
If you're gonna live under our roof, you're gonna follow our rules.
很好 反正我不用再住你们家了
Well, that's good 'cause I don't need to live under your roof anymore,
- 因为今晚起 我的房子就能住了 - 好
- because as of tonight, my apartment's ready.- Good.
- 很好 - 想想你的将来
- Great. - Think about your future!
- 亲爱的 没必要吼的 - 我没吼
- Honey, we don't need to yell. - I'm not yelling!
事实上 我是在吼
Actually, I was yelling.
- 可我不后悔 - 太不公平了
- And I regret nothing! - This is so unfair!
Penelope Hartz 我叫你玩一玩
Penelope Hartz, when I said for you to have a fling,
是指和Shaun那样的正常好男生
I meant with a nice, normal boy like Shaun...
- 正常男 - 而不是我的猪头老板
- Normal boy! - Not my... pig of a boss.
说不定这不是玩玩的 而是真爱
Well, maybe it's not a fling. Maybe it's love.
你有没有想过 说不定我爱他
You ever think of that, Jane? Maybe I love him.
我回来拿钥匙 可你打开了我的心
I came back to get my keys, and you unlocked my heart.
Penny
Penny...
我也爱你
I love you, too.
恭喜 一对爱侣
Congratulations, lovebirds.
这是噩梦
This is a nightmare!
再次感谢 凯蒂猫 让我在这住一会
Thanks, again, kitty cat, for letting me crash here a while.
我得找地方装引体向上的杠
I gotta find a place for my chin-up bar.
我有根和Paul Ryan一样的
I got the same one as Paul Ryan.
我们体型一样 完全可以穿他的衣服
We have the same bod. We could totally share clothes.
此刻我觉得和你好亲近
I feel so close to you right now.
如果你出对牌
You know, if, uh, you play your cards right,
胸前那对宝贝卖力些
you keep those chest pumpkins up and runnin',
我说不定就永久住下了
me moving in could become a permanent thing.
你说多好啊
How great would that be, huh? Huh?
太好了
Suh great.
你们怎么进来的
Hey! How did you guys get in here?
你的大门没了
Your front door's missing.
我需要床头板嘛
Duh. I needed a headboard.
那么明显
Clearly.
你们怎么来了
Why you guys here?
因为我们很抱歉 真心想帮你
Because we're sorry and we really wanna help you.
太迟了 我现在垫底
It's too late. I'm in last place in the competition.
我只赢了一个项目 一口能塞下41个棉花糖
The only event I won was how many marshmallows could you fit in your mouth-- 41.
不迟 今晚就是才艺比赛 占总分一半
It is not too late. Tonight is the talent competition. That's half your score.
如果你赢了 就能赢下整场比赛
If you win that, you could win the whole damn thing.
所以我们想出了一套超牛的表演
Yep. That's why we came up with a kick-ass routine
结合老派格调和新派闪眼
that combines old school class with new school flash.
和火焰
And fire!
火焰太赞了 我同意
Whoa! Fire's awesome! I'm in.
同志们
Uh... guys?
- 原本不是那样的么 - 我以为是
- Is that not normally like that? - I thought so.
那回头见
Well, I'll see you later then.
是我妻子 甜甜 坏消息
That was my wife, sugar face. Bad news.
那老破烂想要我回去
That sweet bag o' garbage is taking me back.
别伤心过度哦
Try not to be devastated.
这很难 但我会尽力的
It's gonna be hard, but I will try.
你的东西在这儿
I just... You know, here's your stuff!
好
Okay.
- 把这些都还给你 - 好
- Give you those babies back. - Okay.
好了
All right.
这段时间挺开心的
Well, this has been fun.
我从没跟有书的女人在一起过
I've never been with a woman who's owned books.
它们是用来看的
They're for reading.
我现在知道了
I know that now.
不
No.
别
No, please.
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
- 我救了你 - 我的天
- I saved you! - Oh, my God!
你吓死我了
Oh, you scared me!
你正对着我的耳朵和整张脸尖叫
Oh, you screamed right in my ear and my-- my whole face!
我们不该交换备用钥匙的
We should not have copies of each other's keys.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我不该对你指手画脚的
Look, it wasn't right of me to tell you what to do.
- 这是你的生活 - 谢谢
- This is your life. - Thank you.
话虽如此
That being said...
我打电话给汽车沙皇的妻子
I called the Car Czar's wife, worked a little Jane magic.
给了她两张加拿大骑士芭蕾的票
Got her two tickets to that Canadian horse ballet.
- "骑士" - 对
- "Cavalia"? - Yeah.
Larry King说那是他看过的最棒的演出
Larry King says that's the greatest show he's ever seen.
你不生气吗
You're not mad?
不 我很抱歉跟你老板啪啪了那么多次
No. I'm-- I'm sorry that I had so much sex with your boss.
- 在你家 - 没关系
- In your house. - That's okay.
- 在你地板上 - 好吧
- On your floor. - Yeah.
在你的打印机上
On your printer.
Penny 我的惠普打印机吗  你不是吧
Penny, my deskjet? Come on, bro.
说实话 你的建议很好
But honestly, your advice was great.
我的确需要玩玩
I needed a fling.
我挺庆幸汽车沙皇那么烂
And I'm glad that the Car Czar was such a pig,
这样我就不会投入真感情
because I didn't get emotionally invested.
我都不知道他的名字
I don't even know his name.
是Lon
It's Lon.
我居然跟一个叫"Lon"的上床了
Ew. I had sex with a "Lon"?
- Lon? - 那不能是人的名字吧
- Lon? - That is not a human name.
头脑发热嘛
Welp... heady times.
以上是Billy Carson的美臀木偶秀
That was Billy Carson's puppetry of the butt!
情景取自上周的"另类家庭"
With a scene from last week's "The New Normal."
下一位 有请Max Blum
Next up, here's Max Blum!
Maxie
Maxie!
小贱人花样真多
Oh, you tricky bitch.
我觉得我爱上你了
I think I love you.
天哪 我真那么说了么
Oh, my God. Did I just say that?
感谢你们今晚的大力支持
Guys, I wanna thank you so much for your support tonight,
很高兴能跟挚友们共度此刻
and it was awesome to share this moment with my best friends in the world.
这是同志对我说过的最好听的话
That is the nicest thing a homosexual has ever said to me.
- 他怎么会在这 - 我真的控制不住
- Why is he here, Brad? - I have a real disease.
今晚最酷的就是
And the coolest part about tonight
我能用自己赢来的钱付账
is that I get to pay for dinner with my winnings.
- 来吃的 - 谢谢
- Food! - Thanks!
离扯平还远着呢
That doesn't even begin to make up for it.
我让他们给我硬币 这是我唯一还信任的货币
I had them pay me in pennies because it's the only currency I still trust.
硬币(Penny) 罐子(胸器)
Oh! Oh! Penny! Jugs!
等等 我在想个段子
hold on. I got a joke brewin' in here.
等等
Uh... okay. Okay.
再等一下 等一下
Hold on. Hold on.
不 等等 再过一会
- Here we go. - Oh! No, wait. Wait. Hold on.
我想出来了
Oh, I got it!
<font color=#38B0DE>-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径</font>
<font color=#70DB93>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-  Sync:óD???à?ê</font>
<font color=#38B0DE>-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: Bella Iphigenie cici 校对: 王棫垚 时间轴: 有志青年</font>
<font color=#70DB93>Happy.Endings S3 Ep20</font>